plink.com 2013-08-20

# Plink.com | Earn Plink Points for Dining and Shopping Offline

#### Date Last Revised: June 05, 2013

Plink has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [support@plink.com](mailto:support@plink.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request). The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, https://www.plink.com.  

At Plink, our relationship with you is our most important asset. We want to earn your trust by being transparent about how Plink works. You should read this policy in its entirety, but should pay particular attention to these highlights: 

  * Plink is an online program where you can earn virtual currency and other rewards from Plink by visiting and making offline purchases at restaurants and other offline merchants. Plink uses a permissions-based tracking system to verify offline purchases. Consumers participating in the Plink program must opt-in to be tracked in the method outlined below. 
  * Plink does not charge for its services; however, to earn virtual currency, you must make offline purchases at participating offline restaurants and merchants. Plink also derives revenue from advertising and marketing services. We do not share, sell, trade or rent your personal information with third parties without your consent. Your privacy is not for sale. We allow advertisers to select characteristics of users (such as location) they want to show their advertisements or make offers to and we use the information we have collected to serve those advertisements and make those offers. We share reports with advertisers using non-private or non-personal information collected in aggregate. 

### Introduction

###### Questions.

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy and Security Policy, contact our privacy team by emailing [support@plink.com](mailto:support@plink.com). You may also contact us by mail at 2000 S. Colorado Blvd, Tower 1 Suite 7000, Denver, CO 80222. 

###### Scope.

This Privacy and Security Policy describes Plink's policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information on www.plink.com. It does not, however, apply to entities that Plink does not own or control. Plink receives your information through our various web sites, APIs, services and third-parties (the "Service"). When using our Service you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy and Security Policy. Irrespective of which country that you reside in or create information from, your information may be used by Plink in the United States or any other country where Plink operates. 

###### No information from children under age 13.

If you are under age 13, please do not attempt to register for Plink or provide any personal information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under age 13, please contact us by emailing [support@plink.com](mailto:support@plink.com). 

### Information Collection and Use

###### Personal information.

Plink is committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity and security of any personal information about our users. "Personal information" for purposes of this Policy means information that identifies you, such as your full name and email address. 

###### Location Information.

Location information, such as the city or zip code where you live, may be collected as part of your Plink profile. 

###### Additional Information.

We may use your contact information to send you information about our Service or to market to you on behalf of third-party advertisers. You may unsubscribe from these messages by following the instructions contained within the messages or the instructions on our web site. If you email us, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request. 

###### Registration.

Plink requires registration, which involves providing Plink an email address, username and password (collectively the "Registration Information"). In order to benefit from the full functionality of the Service, you also must provide your third-party bank account credentials ("Account Credentials") to allow Plink to access your account data at those other institutions ("Account Information") for your use. 

###### Log Data.

Our servers automatically record information ("Log Data") created by your use of the Service. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, the referring domain, pages visited, and search terms. Other actions, such as interactions with advertisements, may also be included in Log Data. This information may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues, or it may be analyzed to improve our Web design and functionality. 

###### Cookies.

Like many websites, we use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Service. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. Plink may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Service, and to improve our Service. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you choose to eliminate cookies, the full functionality of the Service may be impaired for you. We may link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our site. 

The use of cookies by our third party analytics service is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our third party analytics service uses session ID cookies to provide data on how the Plink site is used. Our third party partners employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), images, and scripts that help them better manage content on our site. We do not tie the information gathered to our Customers' or Users' personal information. 

###### Third Party Analytics Services.

Plink uses third party analytics services such as Google Analytics to help understand use of our Service. Google Analytics collects the information sent by your browser as part of a Web page request, including cookies and your IP address. Google's Privacy Policy governs use of this information. Plink is evaluating equivalent analytics services to use in addition to Google Analytics, and we may update this policy in the future to reflect our ongoing use of said services. 

###### Notifications and E-Mail Newsletters.

Plink may use your information to deliver to you any administrative notices, notification alerts, weekly or daily activity summaries, and communications relevant to your use of the Service. From time to time we may also transmit emails promoting Plink or third-party goods or services. Plink subscribers have the ability to opt-out of receiving our promotional emails by following the instructions in the emails or by logging into their account and changing their email preferences. Opting out in this manner will not end transmission of service-related emails, such as email alerts. 

###### Contests, Giveaways and Surveys.

From time to time, Plink may offer you the opportunity to participate in contests, giveaways and other promotions. Any information submitted in connection with such activities will be treated in accordance with this Privacy and Security Policy, except as specifically set forth in the rules for those contests, giveaways or promotions. From time to time, Plink may also ask you to participate in surveys designed to help Plink improve the Site. Any personal information provided to Plink in connection with any survey will be used only in relation to that survey and as elsewhere set forth in this Policy. 

###### Facebook Connect.

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network. 

###### Testimonials.

We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web site which may contain personal information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you want your testimonial removed please contact us at [support@plink.com](mailto:support@plink.com). 

###### Social Media Features.

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

###### Your Consent.

We may share or disclose your information with your consent, such as when you use a third party web client to access your Plink account. 

###### Service Providers.

We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us such as a financial platform provider to help us track your purchases. We may share your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to obligations mirroring the protections of this privacy policy. 

###### Law and Harm.

We may disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request such as a subpoena, or similar legal process; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Plink's rights or property. 

###### Business Transfers.

If the ownership of all or substantially all of our business changes, we may transfer your information to the new owner so that the service can continue to operate. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 

###### Non-Private or Non-Personal Information.

Plink may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated, anonymous or otherwise non-personal information and disclose such data only in a non-personally identifiable manner to: 

  * Advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes, such as the number of users who shopped at a particular retailer or how many users clicked on a particular Plink Offer;
  * Users of the Service for purposes of comparison of their personal spending habits relative to the broader community.

Such information does not identify you individually. Access to your Registration Information, Account Credentials, Account Information and any other personal information you provide is strictly restricted and used in accordance with internal procedures and safeguard governing access, in order to operate, develop or improve the Service. These individuals have been selected in accordance with our security policies and practices and are bound by confidentiality obligations. They may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

### Modifying Your Personal Information

###### Changing your personal information.

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct it by logging into your account and making the change within your account center or contacting us via email at [support@plink.com](mailto:support@plink.com). 

###### Deleting your account.

You can delete your account by issuing a request via email to [support@plink.com](mailto:support@plink.com). When you request us to delete your account for the Service, your data will be permanently expunged from our primary production servers and further access to your account will not be possible. We will also promptly disconnect any connection we had established to your Account Information and delete all Account Credentials. However, portions of your data, consisting of aggregate, anonymized data derived from your Account Information, may remain on our production servers indefinitely. Your data may also remain on a backup server or media. Plink keeps these backups to ensure our continued ability to provide the Service to you in the event of malfunction or damage to our primary production servers. We also reserve the right to use any aggregated or anonymous data derived from or incorporating your personal information. We will also retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

###### Backup copies.

Removed and deleted information may persist in backup copies, but will not be available to others. 

### Your Information Is Secure

###### Access controls.

We use a combination of firewall barriers, encryption techniques and authentication procedures, among others, to maintain the security of your online session and to protect Plink accounts and systems from unauthorized access. However, no security procedures are 100% effective, so there is always some risk that your personal information will be accessed by unauthorized persons. 

###### Access password.

When you register for the Service, Plink requires a password from you for your privacy and security. Plink transmits information such as your Registration Information for Plink or Account Credentials securely. We maintain strict rules to help prevent others from guessing your password. Your password must be at least 6 characters in length. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your Login ID and Password. You may not provide these credentials to any third party. If you believe that they have been stolen or been made known to others, you must contact us immediately at [support@plink.com](mailto:support@plink.com), but in any event you should change your password immediately via the Service. We are not responsible if someone else accesses your account through Registration Information they have obtained from you or through a violation by you of this Privacy and Security Policy or Plink's Terms of Use. 

###### Encrypted communications.

All communications of your password, Account Credentials communications, and other sensitive information between your computer and Plink are encrypted. This enables client and server applications to communicate in a way that is designed to prevent eavesdropping, tampering and message forgery. 

###### Database encryption.

Our databases are protected from general employee access both physically and logically. We encrypt your Service password so that your password cannot be recovered, even by us. All backup drives and tapes also are encrypted. 

###### Third Parties.

It is important to understand that these precautions apply only to our Site and systems. Plink exercises no control over how your information is stored, maintained or displayed by third parties or on third-party sites such as links to advertiser sites. 

###### Links to other sites.

Our Site may include links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Plink. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

###### Security concerns.

If you have a security related concern, please contact us at [support@plink.com](mailto:support@plink.com). We will work closely with you to ensure a rapid and personal response to your concerns. 

###### Changes in this Privacy Statement.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate, prior to the change becoming effective, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. 

###### Contact information.

If you have questions, comments, concerns or feedback regarding this Privacy and Security Policy or any other privacy or security concern, send an e-mail to [support@plink.com](mailto:support@plink.com). 

Plink, Inc.   
2000 S. Colorado Blvd   
Tower 1, Suite 7000   
Denver, CO 80222
